mensflair.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy | Men's Flair

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers information collected on Mensflair.com and does not cover information collected on sites linked to from Mensflair.com.

As a condition of using the Mensflair.com, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be modified. If modified, revisions will appear on this page. Regular access of Mensflair.com by you will designate your acceptance of any changes to the Privacy Policy.

_What information we collect?_

On Mensflair.com, you may ask questions, suggest articles and content improvements, vote in polls, express an opinion, subscribe to our online newsletter, or take part in any interactive section of Mensflair.com. The types of personally identifying information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, and information about your interests. We also may collect certain technical information such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider.

_Why we collect this information?_

Mensflair.com uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, or to improve the services that we offer. Mensflair.com uses the technical information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site. We may use this information to analyze website usage, as well as to provide you with improved services. However, our users who are ones indicated they want to be contacted at their e-mail adress are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of further receiving these communications.

_Who sees this information?_

We do not sell or rent e-mail addresses or your any other personally identifying information obtained through Mensflair.com website to any other organization. We have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access for misuse of information that we have collected from you. Database containing personally identifying information may be provided only for the purpose of cooperating with police investigations or other legal proceedings when we are legaly required to provide access to our database.

_DoubleClick DART Cookie_

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.mensflair.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.mensflair.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

If you have any questions or concerns about the Mensflair.com Policy you may contact us [here](http://www.mensflair.com/contact/).
